https://www.wholesalechess.com/pages/customer-service/your-privacy-security.html

USD
()
More
Chess 101 (The Basics)
PRIVACY POLICY
Your privacy is most important to us. We will never share your personal information with anyone. If you have any questions about this privacy policy please contact us.
YOUR INFORMATION
Wholesale Chess does collect information from its users - we have to in order to sell you the Chess you want! But we assure you that any information you provide to Wholesale Chess will be used only as you expect - to sell you the best Chess at the lowest prices. We only collect information relevant to your shopping experience. In fact, you may browse the site without giving us any personal information at all. You will only be asked to provide information when you start the checkout process or if you voluntarily signup for our occasional email list. We may ask you for any of the following information: name, organization (if applicable), shipping address, billing address, billing information (such as a credit card number, expiration date, etc), and your communications preferences. Information that is optional will be noted. We only use the information we collect to process your orders, manage your account, or send you information that you have specifically requested. We don't customize your experience based on information we receive.
COMMUNICATIONS SETTINGS
If you choose to sign up for our mailing list you will receive occasional communications from us about Wholesale Chess only. We will never send you anything unrelated to Wholesale Chess or Chess in general. You may change your communications setting at any time by clicking the update link at the bottom of any email you receive. We always honor Unsubscribe requests!
YOUR PRIVACY
We don't sell or share your information with anyone. Period. End of story. We don't even use it to customize your shopping experience in any way. It is only used to complete the transactions you want.
BROWSER PRIVACY AND COOKIES
Cookies are small files that store a unique code that identifies your shopping experience. You need to have "cookies" enabled to use our site. However, we do not store any personal information in those cookies. Using cookies does NOT make your shopping experience less secure. The vast majority of online shopping sites require cookies to be enabled.
SECURITY
Your information is stored on our SECURE servers which are located in the United States. Only we have access to the information you submit to us. Your credit card info, email address, and contact info are safe with us. We use good practices such as firewalls, encryption, and Secure Socket Layers (SSL 128bit Security) to protect your data. We have a security certificate from Geotrust, a premier Internet Security validation firm. You will see that our pages are secure because your browser will display a small lock on the bottom status bar, and the pages will begin with "https://" instead of just "http://". If you have any questions about our security, please contact us!
×
OK
Newsletter Signup
Email Address
Categories
New Items
Chess Sets
Chess Pieces
